VINOTH RSYSTEM ENGINEER & FREELANCER

58, 2nd Cross, Periya Kulathu Palayam, Vengamedu, Karur-6

+91-8807515505

vinohard@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

I am a qualified and professional Freelance System Engineer with 8+ years of System Sales and Service and 4+ years of experience in Freelancing and 2+ years in LaTeX coding. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE:

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

SYSTEM ENGINEER | 2014 - Present

- Responsibilities were troubleshooting all kinds of Desktops, Laptops, Assembling systems, installing standard software and maintaining desktops after sales under AMC.
- Installing all windows based Operating systems and applications.
- Installation & troubleshooting of Network Printers and other hardware products.

FREELANCER | 2018 - Present

- Tamil Transcription
- Logo Designing
- Data Entry

PRODUCTION EDITOR | TEXBYTE SOLUTIONS - KERALA | 2022 - Present

- Text processing and Formatting for research and scientific journals
- LaTeX Pagination
- Proof Reading

EDUCATION:

2006 - 2009 | K.K.C. college, P.Velur, Namakkal

Bachelor of Computer Science

2009 - 2011 | Govt. Arts College, Karur

Master of Computer Science

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Father's Name
Date of Birth
Nationality
Maritial Status
Religion
Rajamanickam G
09/03/1989
Indian
Married
Hindu